// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'Collective Animal Names',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What do you call a group of Bats?', 
      a: 'Flock', 
      b: 'Clock',
      c: 'Cauldron',
      d: 'Batmen or Batwomen',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call a group of Jaguars?', 
      a: 'Shadow', 
      b: 'Trip',
      c: 'Sawt',
      d: 'Pack',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call a group of Lemurs?', 
      a: 'Left', 
      b: 'Conspiracy',
      c: 'Colony',
      d: 'Pack',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call a group of Eagles?', 
      a: 'Convocation', 
      b: 'Oval',
      c: 'Branch',
      d: 'Nothing because they\'re solitary',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call a group of Frogs?', 
      a: 'Navy', 
      b: 'Force',
      c: 'Troop',
      d: 'Army',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call a group of Otters?', 
      a: 'Outlet', 
      b: 'Funk',
      c: 'Bustle',
      d: 'Romp',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call a group of Elephants?', 
      a: 'Parade', 
      b: 'Thunder',
      c: 'Bundle',
      d: 'Movement',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call a group of Gorillas', 
      a: 'Gall', 
      b: 'Band',
      c: 'Mob',
      d: 'Orb',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call a group of Ferrets?', 
      a: 'Business', 
      b: 'Mullet',
      c: 'Party',
      d: 'Foil',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call a group of Flamingos?', 
      a: 'Troop', 
      b: 'Sord',
      c: 'Stand',
      d: 'Brace',
      answer: 'c'
    }
  ]
};